Search

1. [Home](https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/)
2. Privacy Policy

**Share page:**[](https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/privacy-policy)[](https://www.twitter.com/share?url=https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/privacy-policy)[](mailto:?subject=Privacy%20Policy&body=Privacy%20Policy:%20https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/privacy-policy)

Privacy Policy
==============

**Construction Forestry Maritime Mining and Energy Union Website Privacy Statement**

This is the Privacy Statement for the Construction Forestry Maritime Mining and Energy Union website.

This is the Privacy Statement for the Construction Forestry Maritime Mining and Energy Union website which is subject to review by the governing body of the Union from time to time.

The Construction Forestry Maritime Mining and Energy Union is committed to the privacy principles issued by the Australian Privacy Commission.

**The information we collect**

Generally, we do not collect personal information about you when you visit our website. You can visit the most parts of the site without being required to provide personal details.

We, or our authorised service providers may use cookies and other similar technologies for storing information to help provide you with a better, faster, and safer experience.

For statistical purposes our web server records all visitors to our site but we are unable to identify individual IP addresses from this data.

If you send us a request by email your email address, and any other personal information you choose to include, is revealed to us.

If you subscribe to our "email updates" list an email is sent to us from our web server which provides your email address.

If you request information about becoming a member of the Construction Forestry Maritime Mining and Energy Union, we collect your name, address, contact phone number occupation and name of employer and your email address.

**How we use the information**

The data collected by our web server is used to assess how many visits to the site we receive and which parts of the site are most frequently accessed. We cannot identify individual visitors to the site from this data.

If you send us a query, request or comment your email address is used to reply to you and for no other purpose. Your email address (and any other personal information you have chosen to send to us) is not retained.

The alert sent to us when you subscribe to our email updates list is used to tally the number of subscribers to the website and for no other purpose. We do not collect your email address from the alert.

If you send a request for more information about joining the union your name and address is used to post you a membership kit. We use occupation and employer information to help assess whether you are eligible to join the union. This information is not retained.

We do not sell or distribute any of the personal information you send to us via our website to any outside organisation, company or individual.

**Data Security**

We use appropriate technology to protect the data we collect.

**Links to other sites**

The Construction Forestry Maritime Mining and Energy Union website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites and suggest that you read each site's policy statement.

Stay Informed

 Name \*

 Email \*

 Postcode \*

Submit  

Can't Find What You Need?

Wages, RDO calendars and other information can be found on your branch page.

Your Union
----------

The Construction, Forestry and Maritime Employees Union is Australia's main trade union in building, construction, shipping, diving, timber, pulp and paper, textile, clothing and footwear industries. The Construction, Forestry and Maritime Employees Union has offices in all capital cities in Australia and in many major regional centres. The union has over 115,000 members and employs around 330 full time staff and officials.

Contact
-------

##### Construction, Forestry and Maritime Employees Union

(03) 9274 9201    [nationalqueries@cfmeu.org](mailto:nationalqueries@cfmeu.org) Level 6, 540 Elizabeth Street, Melbourne, Vic, 3000

Quick Links
-----------

* _[RDOs](https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/rdos)_
* __[Stand up. Speak out. Come home.](http://www.standupspeakoutcomehome.org.au/)__
* __[Our jobs. Our kids. Our future](http://ourjobs.org.au/)__

Connect With us
---------------

Construction, Forestry and Maritime Employees Union [Stand up. Speak out. Fight back.](https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/campaigns)

© Copyright 2024. All rights reserved. [Privacy Statement](https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/privacy-policy) [Sitemap](https://www.cfmmeu.org.au/sitemap)

Authorised by C Cain, Construction, Forestry and Maritime Employees Union National Secretary, Melbourne

  Select Division & Branch
--------------------------

#### [National Office](http://www.cfmeu.org.au/)

#### [Construction & general](#)

#### [Manufacturing](http://manufacturing.cfmeu.org.au/)

#### [Maritime Union of Australia Division](http://www.mua.org.au/)
